THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
您已到达目的地
You have arrived at your destination.
你来晚了
You're late.
也就十分钟吧 外公
Well, like, ten minutes, Grandpa.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving!
印第安人可不快乐
Not for the Indians.
可不是嘛
No, sir.
可不是 现在看来... 也是事实
Nope, that is... still true.
要不咱们随便吃点东西再上路
So, shall we grab some lunch and then hit the road?
我肚子饿得咕咕叫
I gots the old rumblin' tum.
别了 咱们要趁雪下起来前动身
No. Let's go before it snows.
翻译: 奶啾
翻译: 我的后面是猪精
翻译: Shirley Q
翻译: 这个家伙
翻译: 皮带断了
翻译: 宇宙万宝路
翻译: 海顿
翻译: 豆
时间轴: Heiforn
时间轴: 阿布
特效: 雨人
后期&压制: Jason肖
校对:渡渡
校对：宇宙万宝路
继     承
第 一 季  第５集
"我去超市"
监制: 宇宙万宝路
-肯  -什么
- Ken. - Yeah.
我觉得你爸可能想听听你的意见
I think your dad might appreciate your input.
小罗
Uh, Ro.
... 这个 我们还有...
...this, and we have...
伙计们 小心喽
Oh, look out, folks.
"顶尖头脑"来了
Here come the top minds.
你们忙活什么呢
So, what you got cookin'?
真的用不着 先生们
Really no need, gentlemen,
弗兰克想让你参与讨论
Frank wanted to fold you in on this,
但你大概也清楚我对一些事的想法
but you should know, probably, my thinking in terms of things.
有个潜在机会
There's a potential opportunity
做些收购跟合并
for some acquisitions and consolidation.
几家本地电视台
Packet of local TV stations.
本地电视台吗
Local TV?
爸 现在没人看电视
No one watches TV, Dad.
恰恰相反 绝大部分人通过看电视获取新闻
No. TV is where the majority of people get their news.
相对于其他 人们更爱看本地电视台
More people watch local than any other kind.
也不算吧
Yeah, but not really.
我能看到短期内的进项
I could see short-term we make some cash,
但我只是觉得 对韦斯达来说
but I'm just saying, for Waystar,
这么做不掉身价吗
is this a good look?
给你们讲一个花哨的新潮经营理论
There's this fancy new business theory.
名字叫"只要挣得比你花得多 你就是屌王"
It's called "Make more than you spend and you're King Cunt."
爸 别逗了
Dad, come on.
我们凭什么不能垄断新闻业呢
Why shouldn't we do all the news?
-说说看  -我告诉您啊 独裁老爷子[金正爸]
- Yeah. - Well, Kim Jong Pop,
因为在这个国家 这么做是行不通的
because that's not how things work in this country.
你就是喜欢控制人们的思想
You just love telling people what to think,
-对吧  -滚
- don't you? - Fuck off.
人们选择咱们是因为我们不向他们灌输任何东西
People come to us because we don't sell them on anything.
既没什么狗屁慈悲心肠
No packet of fuckin' bleedin' heart
也没有联合国 沃尔沃 异装大佬那些胡诌
United Nations Volvo gender-bender horseshit.
一旦搅和到政治上就会很难看
The politics on this would be horrible.
司法部 美国联邦通讯委员会 反垄断
Justice, FCC, anti-trust.
要受好几年的束缚
We'd be tied up for years.
不会 电视台完蛋了
Nah. TV's fucked.
世上最大的火鸡
韦斯达影业
今秋献映
需要合并
It needs to consolidate.
好吧 我不想小题大做
Fine. I don't want to make this a thing.
既然你喜欢本地电视台 行 你很明智
You like local TV, great. You're smart.
我只是希望能继续追求多样化
I just hope it doesn't mean we can't pursue diversification
-与革新性  -那是当然
- and innovation. - Of course!
印度 中国...
India, China...
你知道印尼有他妈多少人吗
Do you know how many fuckin' people are in Indonesia?
-罗曼  -怎么了
- Roman. - Hmm? What?
可不 谁说不是呢
Uh, yeah, sure. Who doesn't?
远超你的想象 好像十个亿吧[实际约三亿]
It's more than you think. Like, a billion.
罗曼 你就是个白痴
Roman, you're a moron.
你该回去替我们全面掌控 肯德尔
You should get back into all that for us, Kendall.
回去干什么
Get back into what?
做副总
Vice-president.
数字的 全球的
Digital. Global.
在迪拜 印度 中国或随便哪儿建个办事处
Based out of Dubai, India, China-- wherever.
不好意思 你他妈开玩笑呢
Excuse me. Are you fuckin' serious?
散会 都给我滚
Meeting over. Fuck off.
爸
Dad?
爸 那啥 停 停 停
Dad! Hey! Whoa, whoa! Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
打住 打住 我来
Stop. Stop. Got it.
我勒个擦
Oh. Shit.
搞得到处都是啊
That's a big fuckin' mess.
身上没溅到吧
Get any on ya? No?
我找人给清理一下吗
Get someone to clean this up?
好吗
Yeah?
爸 你没事吧
You all right, Dad?
没事 好着呢
Yeah. Fine.
漫漫长路啊
A long drive, eh?
我能理解
I get it.
老妈有个朋友就害怕坐飞机
You know, Mom had a friend who was afraid of flying,
但他却死于一场车祸
but he actually died in a traffic accident.
他当时骑着自行车
Uh... And he was on a bike
还磕了好多药
and heavy meds.
但这个... 挺酷的
So, but this is... this is cool.
就咱们俩 全程就咱俩
It's just you and me, we got this whole time
可以天南地北地聊个够
to talk about whatever, you know,
谈谈生意 什么的
business, uh, stuff,
未来公司... 你懂的
the... the future corporate... ya know,
然后放着乡村音乐
or just let the country music play.
不听音乐 不要聊天
No music. No chatter.
你专心开车
Keep your mind on the driving.
预计用时12小时12分钟
今天的会议很重要
Big meeting today.
但也没什么正经事 就是工作...
Nothing serious, just work, so...
-有点睡不着觉  -我也睡不着
- Yeah. Couldn't sleep. - Yeah, me neither.
有时候我觉得我睡着了 但其实我没有 可奇怪了
Sometimes I thought I was asleep, and then I wasn't. I was weird.
你那大呼噜 猪都打不出来...
Well, you were snoring like a hog, so...
我的通气鼻贴掉了嘛
Yeah, well, my nasal strip fell off.
-这是什么  -婚前协议
- What's this? - It's the pre-nup.
好家伙 行
Whoo-hoo-hoo! OK!
-可还行  -还行吗
- Ahh. Yeah. - Yeah?
意味着动真格的了 咱们要结婚了
It means it's really happening. We're getting married.
你对婚前协议的看法相当浪漫啊
That is a very romantic way of looking at a pre-nup.
你猜怎么着 我连看都不会看
You know what? I am not even gonna look at that.
就告诉我在哪儿签字
Just show me where to sign.
汤姆 你还是应该看一下的
Tom, you have to look at it.
不 听我说 亲爱的 我不是有钱人家的公子
No, listen, honestly, honey, I'm not from money,
你才是有钱人家的闺女... 我不会看的
you're from money... I don't wanna look at it.
...我遵从一切安排
Just... I hereby comply.
我不用你遵从一切安排
I don't want you to comply.
那不是正常婚恋关系的基础
That is not the basis for a healthy relationship.
行吧 行吧
Fine. Fine.
作为我真心爱你的姿态
As a gesture of my love to you,
我会让我律师看看 行吗
I will have my lawyer look at it. OK?
可你要知道
But just so you know,
在我心里 我已经签了
in my head, I've already signed it.
行
Ok.
还好吗
How's it goin'?
我听说你父亲好多了
I hear your father's much better.
是的 对
Yup. Yup.
好很多了
So great.
只是想跟你说 在办公室这边
Just to say, though, down in the pig sty,
我们是您项目的铁粉
we're all huge fans of your stuff.
真是创新之举
Innovation.
谢谢
Thank you.
能举个例吗 比如
Like, uh, like what?
所有项目 比如数据存储
Everything. Data storage.
我认识的搞数码的人都很流行
The digital guys I know were all popping.
说句不好听的 但是全麦早餐那点子
Not to sound cheap, but the whole breakfast cereals thing?
没错 伯特兰什锦麦片摆脱了困境 那策略简直牛逼
Yeah, the Bertram muesli was off the hook. That shit was crazy.
你参与那件事了吗
Were you involved in that?
是的
Yes.
...是的 我参与了
...Yes, I was.
我见了那人 西尔维斯特
So, I met the guy. Sylvester.
西尔维斯特
Sylvester?
你也用假名没
Did you use a fake name?
我觉得那是他的真名
I think Sylvester's his real name.
谁会叫西尔维斯特
Who's called Sylvester?
我们雇佣了他 他很平常 合法公民
He's just, we pay him, he's normal, he's legit,
还被记录在册... 他说过这很容易
he's on the record... he says it's easy.
他会解决[绞碎]这个巡航问题的
He's gonna shred this cruise problem away.
好吧 我挺担心的
OK. Well, I'm worried.
你知道吗 在伊朗革命之后
Did you know that after the Iranian revolution,
那些学生把美国使馆里
the students, they taped back together
被绞碎的文件都用胶带粘回去了
the shredded documents from the US embassy?
你知道这事吗
Did you know about that?
他问了很多数据深度清理的事儿
he asked a lot about the digital deep clean,
我说都会很安全 包括邮件和服务器
and I said that was good, emails and servers,
都会被全面销毁 不是只有特定文件
nice and general, not specific.
但当然了 我们也会消除特定文件的
But, of course we'd wiped the specifics.
好极了 所以怎么消除呢
Great. So how does this part work?
-是这样 我们绞碎文件...  -然后呢
- OK. We shred... - Yeah?
...然后另一批人下班后过来
...then some guys come in when we're quiet,
他建议立刻行动 就明天 感恩节
he suggests right away, tomorrow, Thanksgiving,
然后 他们会处理掉不需要的材料
and, they'll dispose of the unwanted materials.
我们只需要有人去绞碎文件
We just need someone to shred
并且在文件存托处签字 把材料领出来
and to sign out the materials from the document depository,
而那个名字会... 那个名字
and that name could... that's a name that could,
就能在东窗事发时... 背点锅
draw some heat were things to go... bad.
我没法去
Well, I can't do it,
绝对不行 毕竟是感恩节
obviously, Thanksgiving.
你可以吗
could you?
我本来可以的
I mean, I could,
只是 只是 你懂的
it's just, it's, you know,
这任务有点...
the task in hand is a little...
我当然懂 肯定的
No, sure. Absolutely.
你需要一个信得过的人
You need someone you can trust,
可谁... 不怕死呢...
but who is... not expendable...
-那就太惨了  -可不是
- That would be horrible. - Oh, no.
当然 我明白
Sure. I get it.
完全明白
Totally. Totally.
确实 咱们又没把人扔到公车底下
Yeah, it's not as if we'd be throwing someone under a bus.
这可是个一夜成名的好机会
It's giving someone an opportunity to shine.
-对吗  -当然啦
- Yeah? - Great.
是啊
Yeah.
-兄弟 怎么样啊  -你好 汤姆
- Hey, buddy! What's up? - Hey, Tom.
怎么样了 我是不是很快又能在办公室里见到你了
What's goin' on? Am I gonna see you in the office anytime soon?
没那么快 其实我正开车...
Not that soon, I'm actually driving...
行 那你预计多久到呢
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. What's your ETA?
十二个小时吧 我... 在加拿大
about 12 hours? I'm... I'm in Canada.
啥玩意
Excuse me?
加拿大
Canada?
老龄化又无聊的加拿大吗
Canada with the healthcare and the ennui?
去哪儿干吗 小鸡仔
Why is that, cock-sock?
我正开车带外公去过感恩节
I'm driving my grandpa down for Thanksgiving.
格雷格 让你外公滚蛋
Oh, Greg, fuck your grandpa.
我开着免提呢 汤姆
You're on speakerphone, Tom!
你不该开免提的 格雷格
Well, I shouldn't be, Greg.
我懂... 我... 但我正开车呢 我不能...
I know... I... But I'm driving, so I can't, like...
我开着免提 还没关呢
So you are. You're still on it.
好吧 格雷格 那就快点吧
OK, Greg, so, um, hurry up,
因为我有个小差事给你 而且
'cause I got a little job for you, and,
我这么好声好气 是因为你开着免提
yeah, I'm being nice, 'cause I'm on speakerphone,
要不是开着免提 我可就
but if I wasn't on speakerphone I'd be being,
怎么说呢 不会那么和蔼了
shall we say, somewhat less agreeable?
-行 行  -对吧
- Yeah, yeah. - Yeah?
那就这样 挂了
All right. See ya.
好的... 还不错吧
So, yeah... It's good.
他就是这么个颠三倒四的人
It's rough and tumble.
你知道吗 他是
You know? He's,
我也叫他小混蛋来着
I call him a dickie, too.
我猜他非常孤独 而且... 很胆小
He's pretty lonely, and... and afraid. I guess.
...快起来
...Come all the way up.
-去你的  -快起来
- Fuck you. - Come all the way up.
来吧 快点 起来
Let's go, come on! Up!
不 不...
Ah, no! No...
天呐 搞毛线啊
Oh, my God, what the fuck!
我觉得我他妈说得很清楚了
I feel like I'm being pretty fuckin' clear
每隔二十四小时 我就需要一点私人空间
I need a modicum of space every 24 hours.
是你的哥哥 他坚持要进来...
It's your brother. He absolutely insisted...
是真的吗 他洒咖啡那件事
Is it true? About the coffee?
什么 爸吗
What, Dad?
可以回避一下吗
Can you give us a minute?
当然是真的 他一直倒 洒得到处都是
Yeah, sure, he kept pouring, and it just went everywhere.
-跟看不见似的  -老天爷 他的状态不对
- Like he didn't even see. - Jesus. He's not right.
本地电视台 本地新闻
Local TV. Local news.
送你这样一则新闻故事
Here's a news story for you:
本地的一位老人
Elderly local man doesn't
并未意识到他正被谷歌强暴
realize he's getting butt-fucked by Google.
我不会回上海的
I am not going back to Shanghai.
他病倒的时候 是我拯救了公司
I saved the company when he was sick.
你听到他跟我说话的语气了吧
Did you hear the way he talked to me?
我还在工作室那会儿 他就是这么跟我说话的
That was his tone the entire time I was at the studio.
兄弟 我懂 特别居高临下
Dude, I know. So patronizing.
天知道印尼有多少人
Who knows how many people live in Indonesia?
谁他妈在乎 滚他妈的印尼
Who actually gives a shit? Fuck Indonesia.
国名听起来像一种病
Sounds like a medical condition.
等到咱们中的一个接手的时候
One of us eventually takes over,
公司就什么都不剩了
there's gonna be nothing left.
就好比问我究竟跟多少人搞过
Like, how many people live in your ass?
-做他妈的春秋大梦  -公司就像是被一个
- Rip Van Fucking Asshole. - It's like the firm's being run
有强迫症的集物癖管理着
by a compulsive hoarder.
这间公司就是个又旧又丑的鬼屋
It's this big old, ugly, spooky house,
然后他就端坐在正中央
and he's all caked up in the middle
被发霉的报纸团团裹住
covered in fucking moldy newspapers
本地新闻还持续报道着
with the local news blaring,
给浣熊投喂"沃登面包"吧
feeding Wonder Bread to raccoons!
不管怎样 你会采取行动吗
Anyway, are you gonna do something?
-我应该做点什么  -那当然
- I should. - Yeah, you should.
让他尊重你的唯一办法
And the only way he'll respect you
就是尽全力摧毁他 因为换位思考一下
is if you try to destroy him, because in your position,
他也会想这么对你
that is exactly what he would try to do.
没错
Yeah.
可我做不到
I can't do that.
显而易见 祝你在上海玩得开心
Well, obviously, so have fun in Shanghai.
工作... 工作挺顺利的 我觉得
Work's... Work's goin' OK, I would say, yup.
努力工作
Workin' hard.
精神崩溃其中一个征兆就是
One of the symptoms of an approaching nervous breakdown
相信所谓的"工作"
is the belief that one's "Work"
非常重要
is ever so important.
伯特兰·罗素说的
That's Bertrand Russell.
伯特兰·罗素: 英国哲学家 数学家 曾获诺贝尔文学奖
是吗 没错
Huh. Yes, indeed.
是的... 我同意
Yes... Yes to that.
但我有时会想
Um, but I sometimes think,
我... 我知道你打理农场很忙
and I.. you know, I know you're very busy with the ranch
而且还忙着阅读 做你的研究
and with you readings and your research,
但我有时想知道 是否会有一天
but I sometimes wonder if one day
你会感兴趣 比如说...
you wouldn't be interested in, like...
放弃董事会的席位 然后放松一下
giving up the seat on the board and just, like, chilling out,
轻松一番 你懂吗
like, just relaxing, you know?
生活就是一场生存竞争
Life is nothing but a competition
宁为刀俎 不为鱼肉
to be the criminal rather than the victim.
也出自伯特兰·罗素
Also Bertrand Russell.
我没有伯特兰·罗素的箴言书
I don't have a Bertrand Russell quote,
因为我... 之前都没听过他
because I just... haven't even heard of him till now,
但我确实有一个警句
but, um, but I do have this one.
有力气就开干
Just puttin' it out there.
晚上好
Good evening.
怎么样
How was it?
-你感觉如何  -好极了
- How do you feel? - Great.
我收到一点消息
I have some news.
尤恩要来过感恩节
Ewan is definitely coming to Thanksgiving.
尤恩吗 胡说 为什么
Ewan? Bullshit. Why?
为什么 因为他说他想来
Why? Well, because he asked and said he'd like to come,
我就答应了
and I said yes.
你真会撒谎
You're a pretty good liar.
家人之间有嫌隙不太好
It's not good to have rifts in the family.
哪是什么嫌隙 他住加拿大... 也是个刺儿头
It's not a rift. He lives in Canada... and he's a prick.
距离你们上次说话有多久了
Uh-huh. And how long since you spoke?
我们给他寄了张破生日贺卡 不是吗
We send him a fuckin' birthday card, don't we?
我并没因此收到感谢
Not that I get any thanks.
听着 我们都知道你回来
Look, so, we both know you didn't come back
不是出于对我父亲的爱
out of love for my father.
我想问的是... 你有什么计划
I guess what I wanted to ask is, um... what's your plan?
听说过忠诚吗
Ever hear of loyalty?
当然 他不是七个小矮人之一吗[没有"忠诚"这个小矮人]
Sure. Wasn't he one of the Seven Dwarfs?
-天啊  -不是吗
- Oh, boy. - No?
对了 那个说唱歌手 他在武当派吗
Oh, he's a rapper. He was in Wu-Tang?
武当派: 美国纽约说唱乐队组合
操 抱歉 我放所有人回家过感恩节了
Fuck. Sorry, I gave everyone Thanksgiving off.
操他妈的
Motherfucker.
好吧
Ok.
-爸不太好  -不好
- Dad's not well. - No.
那些... 商业决定 没有说服力
The... The business decisions, they're not cogent.
都是陈词滥调
It's old man shit.
虽然某种程度上是他说了算
And, you know, in some ways that's his call,
但他在我的地板上撒尿了
but, you know, he pissed on my fucking floor.
万一传出去怎么办 没人愿意提起
What if that got out? No one wants to say it,
但我们可以 因为...
but, uh. We can because...
我们都很爱他 但他的情况不对劲
basically we love him, but he's not OK.
万一他哪天晚上半夜醒来
What about he wakes up one night,
杰夫·贝佐斯: 亚马逊集团董事会主席兼总裁
给贝佐斯打电话
fuckin' calls Bezos,
一美元就卖掉咱们公司呢
and sells us out for a dollar?
-我就是... -肯...
- I just... - Ken...
我在想什么才是最好的
I'm thinking about what's best.
-我老了  -他病了 弗兰克
- I'm an old man. - He's sick, Frank.
你认为真正的洛根会想让我们袖手旁观
Do you think the real Logan would want us to stand by
看着他把自己的心血毁于一旦吗
and watch while he throws it all away?
继续说
Talk more.
这才对
Attaboy.
感恩节快乐 老妈
Happy Thanksgiving, Mom.
是的 我知道 抱歉
Yeah, I know. Sorry.
我们圣诞节再回去看你
Well, we'll see you Christmas.
或者新年
Or New Year's?
可能会 可能吧
Maybe. Maybe.
好了 总之很感谢 好的 谢谢
Uh, anyway, thanks for that. Yeah. Thanks.
没有 没有 我... 我知道
No, no, no, I... I know.
没事 我理解的
No, I understand, yeah.
好的 我也爱你
OK, I love you too.
再见 再见
Bye. Bye. Bye-bye.
-有问题吗  -没有 没事
- Is there a problem? - No, no, it's fine.
-怎么了  -没有啊
- What is it? - No, it's nothing.
只是我的... 我的律师说...
It's just my... my lawyer was saying that...
你是说你妈说吧
You mean your mom says.
她可是双子城德高望重的律师 小西
She's a highly respected attorney in the Twin Cities, Shiv.
当然 那你妈妈说什么
Sure. So what does your mom say?
她说婚前协议有点不合情理
She says that the pre-nup is a little, uh, unconscionable.
这是一个法律术语
That's a legal term.
我不在乎的
I don't care.
好吧
Fine.
我们可以再看一遍
We can look it over.
好的
Ok.
看来我刚被威姆士丹家震慑了呢
Guess I just got Wamsgansed, huh?
我能说什么 她是个狠角色
What can I say? She's a hard-ass.
那么我 你和罗曼一共三人
So, me, you, and Roman make three.
还需要三人才能成压倒性多数
That's three more for a majority.
尤恩不会来 所以他不会投票
Ewan is never there, so he's not voting.
就算他投票也没事 他恨我爸
Even if he did, he hates Dad.
-格丽呢  -格丽 做梦呢
- What about Gerri? - Gerri. Dreaming.
但是我想
But I think, yeah,
如果尤恩不参与投票
if there's no Ewan,
-操  -从这个数字看...
- Fuck. - looking at the numbers...
还行
yeah.
有阿沙
You know, Asha,
罗曼 斯图伊 劳伦斯
Roman, Stewy, Lawrence.
如果你还能让一些怀疑者坚定的话 可以的
If you could firm up a couple of doubters, yeah.
这... 是很有可能的
It's... It's definitely possible.
有总裁从成功的不信任投票中全身而退过吗
Has any CEO ever survived a successful vote of no confidence?
老实说 我觉得他可能在找出路
You know, honestly, I think he might be looking for a way out.
那我们要这么做吗
So are we doing this?
别问我
Don't ask me.
他是你父亲
He's your father.
我会为了他这么做
I'd be doing it for him.
卡尔拉
Carla!
我们把破咖啡豆放哪里了
Where do we keep the fucking coffee beans?
你不是给他们放假了吗
Didn't you give them the day off?
骨干人员没放
Skeleton staff.
不会坠机的飞机
A plane still carries parachutes
还准备着降落伞以防万一呢
even though it doesn't expect to go down.
亲爱的 如果这架飞机真坠机了 我都不想要降落伞
Honey, if this plane goes down, I don't even want a parachute.
我想在坠毁中死去 真的
I want to perish on impact. I really would.
-感恩节快乐  -感恩节快乐
- Happy Thanksgiving! - Happy Thanksgiving.
你好吗
How are you?
很好
Good.
谢谢
Thank you.
-你好  -你好
- Hi! - Hi!
-感恩节快乐  -感恩节快乐
- Happy Thanksgiving. - Happy Thanksgiving.
你看起来很美
You look gorgeous.
-喝点东西吧  -好的
- Have a drink. - Yeah. Right.
不好意思
Oh, excuse me.
开始了
Here we go.
-尤恩  -玛西娅
- Ewan. - Marcia.
-感恩节快乐  -谢谢你
- Happy Thanksgiving. - Thank you.
真高兴你来了
I'm so happy you came.
他住院的时候就说要见你
He was asking for you when he was in the hospital.
是吗 肯定是药物作用
Yeah, well, must have been the drugs.
我知道他很顽固
I know he's tough,
但你俩就是一对争执不休的冤家
but you are a pair of noble stags who cannot stop fighting.
格雷格 谢谢你开车带他过来
Greg, thank you for driving him down.
必须的... 你说什么呢
Oh, absolute... Well, are you kiddin'?
和你度过美好时光很开心 外公
It was nice to spend some quality hours with you, Gramps.
我能问一下 洛根叔叔怎么样了
And how, may I ask, is Uncle Logan doing?
-你知道的 不太好  -是吗
- You know, still down. - Yeah?
但是尤恩 我们一起给他鼓劲 好吗
But Ewan, together, we cheer him, right?
我说了不算 洗手间在哪
It's not up to me. Where's the bathroom?
我的天 太刺激了点
Oh, my God. That is so strong.
是吗
It is?
当然 我不抽这种大麻
Oh, yeah. I don't smoke schwag.
会嗨到飞起
You're gonna get really high.
老天
Oh, man.
别... 别啊
No... No.
我靠
Aw, shit.
"最大的火鸡" 瞧瞧这坨狗屎
"The Biggest Turkey." Look at this shit.
现在他们说
Now they're saying it's
这能破感恩节票房记录
gonna set a record for Thanksgiving box office.
破记录 那可... 真不错啊 不是吗
Record? That's... that's great, right?
毕竟是咱们公司拍的
I mean, that's ours.
"世界上最大的火鸡"... 不是部好电影 格雷格
"The Biggest Turkey in the World"... it's not a good film, Greg.
他在工作室的时候还想中止来着
When he was at the studio he tried to stop it,
但是被蠢货们挡回去了
but he got overruled by the jerkies.
这样啊 尽管如此
Oh. Well, although,
它让罗曼和大家赚更多钱啊
it has made Roman and everyone more money.
格雷格 赚钱不是重点
That's not the point, Greg.
不 不 当然不是了
No. No. Of course not.
你在这儿啊
There you are!
我要再来点酒
I need more booze.
借过 谢谢
Hey. Thanks.
-旅行怎么样  -还不错 伙计
- How was the trip? - Good, man.
我听说尤恩老人家很有个性
I hear Grandpa Ewan's quite a character.
对啊 说得没错
Yeah. It was all right.
我最后发现
I mean, I eventually found
他喜欢冲着一个经济学播客抱怨
an economics podcast he liked to shout at.
是吗
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
听我说 我其实需要你
So listen, I actually need you
今天去一下办公室 可以吗
to go to the office today, is that cool?
我能明天再去吗 因为我刚从加拿大开车回来...
Can I go tomorrow? 'Cause I just drove down from Canada...
-必须今天去  -好吧
- It has to be today. - Yeah.
那里又没人 所以...
No one will be there, so...
-我知道 正因如此  -好吧
- I know, I know. Exactly. - Yeah.
格雷格 咱俩一起经历过艰难险阻...
Greg. You and I have had our bumps...
重要时刻
Big-time.
格雷格
Greg.
但说真的
But really,
我只希望你相信我
I just want you to trust me.
好吧
Yeah.
我也想要相信你
And I want to be able to trust you.
你想让我做什么
What do you want me to do?
跟我没什么关系 而且...
Has nothing to do with me, and...
这段对话从来没有发生过
we never even had this conversation.
伙计 我需要更多细节
I'm gonna need more details, man,
-因为我...  -你只需要...
- because I'm... - All you have to...
听我说 你只需要去一趟办公室
Listen to me. All you have to do is go to the office,
签领一些文件盒子出来 绞碎几张纸
sign out some boxes, do a little bit of shredding,
-见见几位善良的人...  -什么
- meet some lovely guys... - What?
-这就是那种事吗  -格雷格 对
- Is this the thing? - Greg? Yeah.
格雷格 别想得太严重
Don't make it a big deal, Greg.
格雷格 只是小事一桩
Not a big deal, Greg.
黑猩猩都搞得定
A chimp could do it.
小黑猩猩
Little chimpanzee.
-你好  -康纳
- Hi. - Connor.
-感恩节快乐  -谢谢
- Happy Thanksgiving. - Thank you.
-这位是...  -对 威拉
- This is... - Yes. Willa.
我听说你要来 但没想到你真来了
I heard you were coming, but I didn't believe it.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
我听说这是罗根的最爱
I hear this is Logan's favorite.
-谢谢  -客气了
- Thank you. - Yeah.
又一罐 恕我失陪
More. Excuse me.
格丽
Gerri.
这边
Right over here.
-感恩节快乐  -谢谢
- Happy Thanksgiving. - Thank you.
阿诺德·拉合尔 我好喜欢 太感谢你了
Oh! Arnaud Lahrer. J'adore! Merci beaucoup.
他带她来参加感恩节聚会吗
He brought her to Thanksgiving?
你觉得她会收节假日加班费吗
Do you think she charges overtime for holidays?
不太妙 感觉总有一天会演变成丑闻
It's not cool. Like, one day that's a story.
不
Oh, no.
-你懂的  -我懂
- You know that. - I know.
他们干嘛也带越橘果酱
Why'd they bring cranberry sauce too?
别纠结了 你也送不了他啥新奇的
Oh, yeah, forget it. You can't get him anything.
去年圣诞节 我以为自己很机灵
Last Christmas I thought I'd had an idea,
送了一本麦克·阿瑟将军的新传记
new General MacArthur bio?
结果他手头已经有七本了
He got, like, seven copies.
我能吃点甜点吗
Can I have some canapés?
祝你好运
Good luck.
行吧
Yeah.
尤恩为毛来这里
What the fuck is Ewan doing here?
问得好
That is the question.
这会影响你的票数
That would fuck your numbers.
谁的主意
Whose idea was it?
玛西娅的
Marcia's.
好像是
I think.
你爸...
Your dad's...
忽然之间要变动信托
suddenly all about changing the trust,
她邀请我和格丽去参加感恩节聚会...
she invites me and Gerri to Thanksgiving...
还把野人叔叔也引了出来
And lures Uncle Sasquatch out of hiding.
简直想"庆祝"一下
Gotta tip your chapeau to that shit.
尤恩叔叔
Uncle Ewan.
很高兴见到你
It's good to see you.
好久不见了
It's been too long.
对啊 我有同感
Hmm. Likewise.
他在哪
So, um, where is he?
我觉得他可能在休息吧
Uh, he's resting, I guess.
我大老远跑过来 他居然连楼都不下吗
I drove 500 miles, and he can't come downstairs?
他可能还病得厉害 所以...
I guess he's still pretty sick. So...
他的情况有好有坏 但是...
I mean, he's up and about, but, uh...
他... 他跟以前不太一样了
he's... he's not really quite his old self.
他其实...
He's actually...
不  我不该说的
No, I shouldn't say it.
他的行事其实有点奇怪
He's actually acting kind of strange.
比如说邀请我来过感恩节
Like inviting me to Thanksgiving.
没错
Exactly.
最近如何
So, how's it goin'?
小西 为你的女政客感到遗憾
So sorry to hear about your woman, Shiv.
-你说乔伊丝吗  -对啊
- You mean Joyce? - Mm-hmm.
不 她赢了 格蕾丝 她当上了美国参议员
No, she won, Grace. She's a US senator.
不 好像不是的 因为我...
No, I don't think so, because I...
我很确定
I'm pretty sure.
我当时就在场
I was there.
我三天没合眼了
I mean, I was up for 72 hours.
这事对我来说还挺重要
It was kind of a big deal for me.
我受邀担任参议员顾问
I've been asked to be senior advisor.
那就恭喜了
Oh, well, congratulations.
谢谢
Thanks.
-不用  -你做得很好
- No. - You did a great job
因为她真是一点都不可爱
because she was really quite unlikeable.
这是真的
It's true.
我从来没喜欢过她
I never liked her.
是吗
Huh.
为什么
Why is that?
我觉得她有点
I guess she's kind of, you know,
她有点... 虚伪
she's kind of... kind of phony?
有点吓人
Kind of scary?
她想把我所有的钱都卷走
She wanted to take all my lovely money.
没错 太虚假又太真实
Right. So too fake and too real.
我觉得她表现得很像个... 贱货
I guess she just comes off as a kind of a... bitch.
你肯定也经常被这么说吧
But, like, you must get that a lot.
对啊 但在感恩节被家人这么说
Yeah. You know, not usually from family,
还是第一次
at Thanksgiving.
-阿米尔  -妈
- Amir. - Maman.
-你终于来了 -抱歉 我来晚了
- Finalement. - Veillez excuser mon retard.
你能来我就很高兴了
Je suis content que tu sois là.
-那是谁  -我觉得是玛西娅的儿子
- Who's that? - I think it's Marcia's son.
这样啊
Uh-huh.
-那是谁  -跟康纳一起的那个吗
- And who's that? - With Connor?
-对啊  -那是他的妓女
- Mm-hmm. - That is his whore.
搞戏剧的那个女人吗
The woman talking about theater?
他知道吗
Does he know?
那还用问 他可是付她钱给他口呢
Of course. He pays her to suck his cock.
不 不会吧
No. No way.
几年前 是我牵线让他们俩认识
I actually introduced them a few years ago
她那时还在
when she on that hot
"派对辣妹不会看你第二眼"的妓女边界线上
party-girl-who-wouldn't-look- twice-at-you/hooker borderline.
她很可爱 很漂亮
She's cute. I mean, pretty.
-她... 她过来了  -好了 士兵 准备好了吗
- Here she... Here she comes. - OK, soldier, ready?
来谈细节了
Just gettin' the deets.
-懂了  -你们好
- Copy. - Hi.
-感恩节快乐  -感恩节快乐
- Happy Thanksgiving. - Happy thanksgiving.
这是我的堂弟 格雷格
This is my cousin Greg.
他见到你巨激动
He is very excited to meet you.
失陪了
Excuse me.
-你 你好  -你好
- H-Hi. - Hi.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
对
Yeah.
感恩节快乐
Yes.
抱歉 我打扰你们了吗 还是...
I'm sorry, did I interrupt something, or...
不 不 不 我们只是在...
No, no, uh, no. We were just...
我们也没聊什么
We weren't talking about anything,
就说了点 戏剧
we were talking about, uh, theater.
你喜欢戏剧吗
Oh! Do you like theater?
不 不是... 不是... 太喜欢
No. No, not... Not... Not really.
我看得不多
I mean, I haven't seen a lot,
但就我看过的 不是太喜欢
but of the stuff I've seen, not really.
其实 我们不用非得谈戏剧
OK. We don't have to talk about theater.
-不 没关系  -好的
- No, good. - OK.
那么问题来了
Oh, well, here's a question.
那个... 如果你被困住
Uh.... would you rather
是宁愿选有鲨鱼的游泳池
be trapped in a swimming pool with a shark
还是有老虎的笼子
or in a cage with a tiger?
这个... 有鲨鱼的游泳池吧 你呢
Um... maybe a swimming pool with a shark. And you?
-我也是  -是吗
- Yeah. Same. - Right?
是啊 真的
Like, yeah, totally.
因为你可以正对着鲨鱼的鼻子砸下去...
'Cause you can punch a shark right in the nose...
过来 凯莫·萨贝 过来一下
Come on, Kemo Sabe. Come on.
-现在吗  -对 过来
- Now? - Now. Come on.
再见
Bye.
-来了 哥们  -来了
- Hey, man. - Hey.
力道不错 很结实 握手伙伴呀
Great handshake. Firm. Handshake buddies.
好的 回见
OK, you. OK.
这些是文件编号 这个是房间号
These are the file numbers, and this is the room number.
没问题吧
Good?
好
OK.
这里的玩笑和氛围让我讨厌
I hate the jokes, I hate the atmosphere,
我想了很久 得出了个想法
and I've been thinking, and I have an idea.
你很优秀...
You're such a great person...
是个厉害的... 作家和制片人
such a great... writer/producer,
我想在事业上帮你一把
I want to help you with your career.
经济方面不用你担心
And the financial aspect of this isn't even a concern.
我可以资助你工作 然后...
I can fund your work. And then...
-好吧 说重点  -我是说...
- OK, how do you mean? - I mean...
我希望我们...
I'd like us...
可以差不多...
to be kind of...
确定关系了
exclusive?
这样你就能不再...
Uh, that way you could stop...
跟别的人约会
hanging out with other people
你的空闲时间就更多了
and you'd have more free time.
专心搞戏剧
For the theater.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
这想法的确很诱人
I mean, it's obviously intriguing.
如果你愿意 可以和我一起住在新墨西哥州...
If you wanted, you could live with me in New Mexico...
-不行  -当然 不过
- No. - Of course, I mean,
只是大概四小时的航程...
you know, it's only like a four-hour flight...
我得留在这里工作
I need to be in the city for my work.
那里也可以工作
Well, that can work too.
-细节以后还能讨论嘛  -当然
- We can discuss the details. - Yeah.
不过你要是能把握住...
It's just so great that you're open to this...
这次... 进一步发展的机会...
uh, this.... this opportunity...
-就太好了  -我明白
- for progression. - Yeah.
很诱人 不是吗
It's intriguing. Isn't it?
扇我的脸
Slap my face.
-扇你吗  -对 扇我脸
- Slap you? - Yeah, slap my face.
你是世界上最好的女朋友
Ooh, you're the best girlfriend in the world.
吻我 吻我
Give me a kiss, give me a kiss.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
谢谢 感恩节快乐
Thank you. Happy Thanksgiving.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
你还好吗
You OK?
当然 还行
Yeah. Yeah.
看谁来了
Look who's here.
是... 尤恩
Well... Ewan.
洛根
Logan.
路上顺利吗
How was the journey?
漫长无比
Incredibly long.
你气色糟透了
You look terrible.
很憔悴
Haggard.
谢谢
Thank you.
是啊...
Yes...
我的身体最近...
I have been...
非常不好
incredibly unwell.
好了 大家伙
All right, everyone.
餐点准备好了
Food is ready.
请就座
Please.
北档案馆
你好啊
What's up?
这些是我要的盒子
Uh, these are the boxes I need.
好 通行证呢
OK. Pass?
你 想必...
And you, presume...
想必你会记录吧
presumably, you keep that,
比如取件人 取件时间什么的
like, that record of who got what, when?
-是啊  -好
- Uh-huh. - Yeah.
那些记录... 都记在哪里
Where does that r... that, like, record go?
这个本子上
It goes in this book.
好 很好
Cool. Great.
没人会看的 是吧
Who cares, right?
那个 我问是因为...
Uh, yeah, I was just asking 'cause...
这些有可能会给第三方看的话
just in terms of like sharing it with third parties,
我希望保护好... 我的隐私
I like to keep... keep my data pretty tight.
谢了 哥... 哥们
Thanks, ma... Thanks, man.
再次 欢迎大家的到来
Again, welcome, everybody.
请随意
Please go ahead.
我们今天吃的是家庭餐
We're eating family-style.
家庭餐啊 搞得我们跟一家人似的
Oh, family style. What, almost like we're a family.
好了
OK.
我来
All right.
十字交叉
Cross intersection.
别客气
Serve yourself.
-谢谢  -那是家庭餐的做法吗
- Thank you. - Is that what families do?
-不用 不了  -好
- No. No. - Yeah.
老爸 切得真好
OK, Pa. Nicely done.
没错
Yeah.
尤恩...
So, Ewan...
农场怎么样了
how's the ranch?
你怎么不哪天过来一趟呢 自己看看
Why don't you come up sometime? See for yourself.
谢谢 尤恩 真是热情的邀请
Thank you, Ewan. What a kind invitation.
大家好 抱歉我们来晚了
Hi! Hi. Sorry we're late.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
来了
Hey.
来了 感恩节快乐 抱歉 路上太堵了
Hi. Happy Thanksgiving. Sorry, we're on the Turkey Trail.
-你迟到了  -你好
- You're late. - Hi.
-来了  -艾弗森呢
- Hey. - Where's Iverson?
他... 他... 他...
He's... He's... He's, um...
他在另一间屋里
He's just in the other room.
他... 他现在情绪不对
He's... He's just having a moment.
抱歉了 大家
Sorry, guys.
-我去陪他坐一会  -不用了 没关系 我去
- I'll go sit with him. - No, it's fine. I will.
不许过去
Don't go there! Hey!
让他进来
Get him in here.
叫他干什么就得干什么
He has to do as he's told.
他只是需要点时间 毕竟离婚过渡期
He just needs some time, because transitions
-很难熬  -或者我们应该...
- are difficult. - Maybe we should just...
是吗 过渡期很难熬
Oh. Transitions are difficult.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
你们知道过渡期困难这回事吗
Did you know that transitions were difficult?
我的确理解过渡期很难熬
I did know that transitions were difficult.
你们有过渡困难期吗
Did you have transition difficulties?
干杯 大家
Cheers, everybody!
干杯
Cheers.
你打我电话干什么 别打给我 有事吗
Why are you calling me? Do not call me. Is there a problem?
什么都别告诉我 你手机都不该开着
Don't tell me anything. Your phone shouldn't even be on.
我在档案库登了记调出了文件箱
I signed at the depository for the document crates,
然后 我进房间了 汤姆 这没问题吧
and, uh, I'm in the room, Tom, is that OK?
-好的 你知道该怎么做  -但这没问题吗 因为...
- Well, you know what to do. - But is it OK? Because...
水门事件: 转喻秘密的 经常是非法的活动
这状况就像水门事件一样
this feels like a Watergate sort of scenario,
虽然我没具体学过
and I never studied that specifically,
但我确实记得 事件里的相关人员都玩儿完了
but I feel like, um, I'm correct in saying they all got fucked.
当然没问题 格雷格
Of course it's OK, Greg!
没事 这是工作
It's OK. It's a job.
把螺栓射进牛头里[宰牛]也是工作
Shooting bolts into cows' heads is a job,
但我不想在感恩节的时候做
but it's not how I want to spend my Thanksgiving.
你懂吧
Ya know?
...喂
...Hello?
天...
Man...
你爸
your dad.
真混蛋
Fuck off.
是 我知道
Yeah, I know.
他做得确实很粗暴
I guess he had it pretty rough.
世代不同
Different generation.
好吧 你回去吧 我来陪着他
OK, you know what? You go back in. I got this.
-本来也都是我的错  -我没这么说 拉瓦
- I'm sure it's my fault anyway. - I wasn't saying that, Rava.
我是说...
I was just s...
我是说也许他
I was just saying maybe he
有时候是该懂得守点规矩
would like to feel where the line is sometimes.
-"厉害"  -真是的 你们
- Wow. - Come on. Guys?
菜要凉了
Your food will get cold.
-知道了  -就来
- Got it. - Coming.
♪ 力挽狂澜[这部分留下] ♪
♪ This saves the day ♪
♪ 力挽狂澜 输家滚蛋[另一部分丢掉] ♪
♪ This saves the day, the other goes away ♪
♪ 力挽狂澜 输家滚蛋 ♪
♪ Saves the day, the other goes away ♪
♪ 格雷格状态正佳 ♪
♪ Greg is choppin' it up ♪
♪ 格雷格状态正佳 格雷格状态正佳 ♪
♪ Greg is choppin' it up, Greg is choppin' it up ♪
♪ 力挽狂澜 ♪
♪ This saves the day ♪
♪ 输家滚蛋 ♪
♪ The other goes away ♪
♪ 力挽狂澜 ♪
♪ This saves the day ♪
它们贵吗
And are they expensive?
有多有少
Varies.
这里的这个
This. Hm, here.
这是维多利亚十字勋章
This is a Victoria Cross.
小罗 你应该研究点这样的事
Rome, you should do something like this.
有个爱好挺好的
It's nice to have a hobby.
-我有爱好  -杀死流浪汉才不是爱好
- I got a hobby. - Killing hobos isn't a hobby.
说得漂亮
Pretty.
再看这个...
And this...
是十六世纪一战加拿大步兵勋章
is a World War I 16th Infantry Canadian medal.
当然了
Of course,
亚述人在罗马人之前就开始带勋章了
the Assyrians wore medals before the Romans.
而这枚... 是罗马帝国
But this... is Roman.
原谅我的无知 但有哪些是你赢得的吗
And, excuse my ignorance, but did you win any of these?
当然没有
Of course not.
他从未服兵役
He never served.
我能不能摸...
Is it OK if I...
-最好别摸  -好吧
- Maybe don't touch. - OK.
这个确实花了大价钱
This one did cost rather a lot.
当初赢得他的人可没花那么多
Not as much as it cost the man who won it.
我收集它们... 是出于尊重
I collect 'em... out of respect.
当然了
Sure you do.
你知道吗 五十年前
You know, 50 years ago
他自愿参战就是为赢得镇上一个荡妇的欢心
he volunteered for a war just to impress the town slut.
可现在 这故事被他没完没了地说
And now, no one... no one... ever hears the end of it.
我以为加拿大人只在冰上打仗呢
I thought Canadians only fought on the ice.
三万加拿大士兵在越南打共产党
30,000 Canadians fought communism in Vietnam.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
谢谢你 感谢 太感谢你了
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
你想要什么 勋章吗
What do you want, huh? A medal?
-让大家自由  -你说什么
- To keep us free. - What?
越南共党顺着下水道爬到渥太华了吗 是吗
Viet Cong come up your drainpipe in Ottawa, did they?
随你怎么恶言相向
Free to spew your poison.
你为每一场我们本不用打的战争狂欢叫好
Carnival barker for all the wars we really didn't need.
你枪都没开过吧
Did you even fire a gun?
你最后不就是个炊事兵吗
Didn't you end up doing KP duty?
请别这样
Oh, please, come on.
应该把尸体寄给你
They should send you the bodies.
你肩负重任 在厨房搅拌秋葵浓汤
Bear any burden. Stir any gumbo.
我家里一个你的频道都没有
I don't have any of your channels at my house.
但我看过...
Oh, I see them...
在我吃面条的馆子里
at the place I go for noodles.
那里有你的频道
They have 'em on.
我觉得很丢脸
And I'm embarrassed.
胡扯
Bullshit.
你不装那些频道是因为你愤愤不平
You don't have 'em because you're bitter.
全球变暖
Global warming?
气候变化
Climate change?
你手上数不清的人命
The blood of millions on your hands?
玩蛋去吧 缩手缩脚上校
To get your fuckin' nut, Captain Cautious.
不是什么事都与钱有关 洛根
Everything isn't about money, Logan.
你就没听过道德一说吗
Have you ever heard of ethics?
那你听过求援信吗
You ever heard of a begging letter?
一封可悲的信
One miserable letter.
我只拥有一千英亩的土地... 而你拥有全世界
I got a thousand acres... you got the rest of the world.
好吧 好吧 好吧
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
大人物 大哥
Big man. Big brother.
吃个破蓝莓都要称一下
Wouldn't eat a fuckin' blueberry until it had been weighed
还要记在小账本上 你个古板小姐
and written in the ledger, little Miss Prim!
你不了解我
You don't know who I am.
你也不是真相的裁决者
And you are not the arbiter of the truth.
当然 当然 老生常谈
Oh, yeah, yeah, heard it all before.
有人告诉我你已经准备好道歉了
I was told that you were ready to apologize.
道什么歉
For what?!
你们都是骗子
You're all liars.
你们欺骗了我
You lied to me.
也羞辱了我
And you humiliated me.
但除此之外 你还是度过了一段美好时光的吧
But other than that, you had a nice time?
滚边儿去
Go fuck yourself.
我不懂为什么我们不每年都请他来
I don't understand why we don't invite him every year.
你出的好主意
Your idea.
过得好吗
How's it going?
那些是... 一大堆公司文件...
That's... a bunch of corporate materials...
还要再碎一回
headin' for an extra shreddin'.
搞定
That's it.
好了 谢谢 谢谢你们
All right, thank you. Thank you.
我好像不该说话
Not supposed to talk, I guess.
我就知道这是个错误
I knew this was a mistake.
-我要回家了  -我们能谈谈吗
- I'm going home. - Can we talk?
...尤恩叔叔
...Uncle Ewan?
没什么可谈的
There's nothing to talk about it.
他是个骗子
He's a liar.
他以为自己在说真话
He thinks he's telling the truth.
-真他妈让人生气  -是 没错
- It's goddamn infuriating. - Yup. Yup.
我从他那得到的只有满嘴垃圾
The only thing I ever got from him was a mouthful of garbage.
他... 他很难搞 确实难搞
He's... He's tough. He is tough.
本以为将死之人能有所改变
You'd have thought nearly dying might have changed him.
好吧 我觉得他变了
Well, I think he has changed.
我觉得他现在状态很不对
I don't think he's himself at the moment.
他的病比看起来更重
Like he's a lot sicker than he's letting on.
-好吧  -他喜怒无常
- Uh-huh. - He's erratic,
不断做着糟糕的决定...
he's making bad decisions...
如果他不小心 就会毁了公司
if he's not careful, he's gonna destroy the company.
你有什么计划吗
And you have a plan?
...是 我在考虑
...Well, I'm considering.
好吧 听着
OK, look.
虽然我从没机会了解你
I never got a chance to know you,
但我一直都很欣赏你 懂吗
but I always liked you. OK?
我准备跟你说件事
I'm gonna say something now.
虽说我这是在冒险
I'm putting my prick on the third rail here,
但下次董事会上
but at the next board meeting,
会进行不信任投票
there's going to be a vote of no confidence.
你对他有信心吗
I mean, do you have confidence in him?
我弟弟已经不是苏格兰人了...
My brother's an ex-Scot...
不是加拿大人 也不是人
an ex-Canadian, an ex-human being.
不过他终归是我弟
But he's still my brother.
尤恩叔叔 你要去哪儿...
Uncle Ewan, w-where are you...
行 我... 我懂了
OK. No, I... I get that.
你觉得他们会和解吗
So do you think it's gonna be OK?
当然 这比我们家最糟的那次感恩节还差远了
Oh, yeah, this was in no way our worst Thanksgiving.
你的律师最近在和我的律师沟通
So apparently, um, your lawyer's talking to my lawyer.
-是你妈  -是的
- You mean your mom. - Yeah.
她对我精子数[后代]的
She's got all excited about
分层认股权关系特别较真
tiered share option tie-ins for my sperm count,
然后我说 "不 不 不"
and I'm goin', "No, no, no."
她提到了有关不忠行为
But she did notice that re: infidelities,
好像没有条款涉及它
there's no clause for that.
对 我们用不着这条
Yeah. We don't need to do that.
确实 我们不会背叛彼此
No. Cause that's not gonna happen.
对 就算发生了 大家都是成年人了
Right. And if it does, we're both grown-ups.
当然
Yes.
什么意思
Meaning?
我是说什么都不会发生
Well, I mean, nothing's gonna happen,
不过你懂的 出差在外难免...
but, you know, things happen with travel, so...
我... 我不会经常出差
Yeah, I... I don't travel that much.
我知道... 重点是 世事难料
Yeah, but... the point is, shit happens.
-世事真的难料吗  -当然不 我们不会
- Does shit happen? - No. No, not to us.
不过世事的确难料
No, but, yes, shit happens,
所以才有"世事难料"这话
that's why we have the expression "Shit happens."
汤姆...
Tom...
我没劈过腿 因为我爱你
I have not cheated on you. Because I love you.
明白 谢谢
OK. Thanks.
我相信她
I believe her.
你信她吗
Do you believe her?
话说回来她是靠培训职业骗子赚钱的
Although she does coach professional liars for a living,
你自己得好好琢磨琢磨
so you do have to factor that in.
我... 我就是想说
I just... I just wanna say
我... 我非常希望你...
I... I would really appreciate it if...
我只是...
You know, I was only...
向周边传达一些想法
kicking some notions around,
-目前还没有定论  -抱歉
- and nothing is set, so... - Excuse me.
我真觉得咱们没必要...
I really don't think we have to make a whole...
我... 我是为了他好
I... I just want what's best for him.
那还用说吗
Uh-huh. Of course.
好儿子
The good son.
"好"极了
It's brilliant.
我... 拐杖忘拿了
I, uh... forgot my stick.
咱们走了
We're leaving.
-什... 什么  -快来 格雷格
- Wh... What? - Come on, Greg.
我才刚回到这儿
It's just, I only just got here again,
明天... 还挺忙的
Tomorrow's... I'm kinda busy,
有很多事情... 等着我... 去做
like, I have a lot... stuff... work... to do here.
我的职责还挺重要的
Like, I'm pretty important here.
我也快饿死了...
I'm starving, too. Like...
那我怎么回家
How am I supposed to get home?
叫优步
Uber.
我可以叫司机 不麻烦的
We can call one of our guys. That's no problem.
好 太棒了
OK. Great. Yeah.
这个家族就是个毒蛇[小人]窝
This whole family is a nest of vipers.
他们会缠绕着你
They'll wrap themselves around you
让你窒息而死
and they'll suffocate you.
我觉得...
I'm pretty sure...
那应该是蟒蛇干的事吧
I'm pretty sure that's boa constrictors.
行了 你
OK, you.
闹够了 给我进去
Enough. Get in there.
-立刻  -洛根 我们...
- Now! - Logan. We...
艾弗森
Iverson.
看见没
See?
谢谢你 谢谢你的支持
Thank you. Thank you for the support.
简直了
That's great.
想都别想
Don't even.
你在干嘛 谁放的电影
What are you doing? Who put this on?
格蕾丝
Gracie.
那你们笑什么
And why are you laughing?
大火鸡把这家人的玉米都吃了
The big turkey just ate the family's corn.
你们真的信了吗
And you think that would actually happen?
这么大的火鸡在后院里
A turkey of that magnitude in the backyard,
大人们却没发觉 怎么可能
and the parents don't notice? How is that possible?
就是说啊
Exactly.
你得躲起来
You've gotta hide!
格蕾丝 我能...
Grace, can I...
不好意思 马上回来
OK. Excuse me. I'll be back.
好好看电影 孩子们
Well, enjoy your movie, kids.
他大概才刚进来...
He probably just got in...
我的天呐
Oh, my God.
搞毛 格蕾丝
What the fuck, Grace?
我到的时候她们就在看了... 电影挺好看的
It was just there, and I... It's actually pretty good.
是吗 我还不知道呢 原来好看啊
Oh, it's good? It is? Really? Oh, I didn't know that. It's good.
-真的很好看吗  -是啊
- Is it really? It's good? - Yeah.
那行 看来咱俩出现不可调解的矛盾了
OK, well, then clearly we have irreconcilable differences,
所以我们得谈谈
so we need to have a talk.
-谈什么  -谈什么
- What talk? - What talk?
我还没到能那啥[结婚]的地步
I'm not in a place right now
这也不是你的问题
where I can blah, it's not you,
而是那啥 我一直都关心那啥
it's blah, I'll always care for blah,
请把我小弟弟的照片留下
please leave those pics of my cock and blahs,
等等等等那啥 就是这种谈话
blah blah blah blah blah. That fuckin' talk.
好 你想谈谈
Oh, OK, you wanna talk
为什么我们大半年才上一次床吗
about how we only fuck once every six months?
滚蛋 你干得还不够多吗
Fuck you. You got plenty.
你就不想谈那事吗
You don't wanna talk about that?
这个话题谈着不好玩吗
That's not fun to talk about?
谈完了 闭嘴 滚你妈的
Just did. Shut up. Fuck you.
-看你的电影去  -操你妈
- Watch your movie. - Fuck you.
妥了吗
Hey. All good?
-都办好了  -我不想知道
- All done. - I don't wanna know,
也别告诉我
and don't ever tell me,
不过你干得漂亮
but well done.
欢迎加入我们家
Welcome to the family.
好了 各位
OK, everyone.
准备吃派了吗
Ready for pie?
-太好了  -来吧
- Yum. - Please.
要是那狗熊
And if by some chance
有那么丁点可能把我从屋顶上推下去
that bear pushes me off the roof,
我就一枪崩了那条狗
I'm gonna shoot that fuckin' dog.
-所以你开枪了  -什么
- So you shot it? - What?
-你开枪了吗  -这是个笑话
- So you shot it? - It was a joke.
-不是真事  -你没听到开头
- It's not an anecdote. - You missed the beginning.
我没听到开头
I didn't hear the first part, yeah.
-你不用听  -没人听到了
- You didn't need to. - Nobody did.
能做件我们家在感恩节做的事吗
Can we do what my family does at Thanksgiving?
干火鸡吗
Fuck the turkey?
去别人家吃饭
Go to other people's dinners.
不是
No, no.
我们轮流 绕着桌子一圈对彼此轮流
We go around, we go around the table and we each say
说感恩的话
what we're thankful for.
行吧
Very well,
我先说
I'll go first.
我感恩全家都聚齐了
I'm thankful to have the family all together.
好
Nice.
我感恩上天没把我生成连体婴儿
I'm thankful that I was not born a Siamese twin.
我同意
I'm also thankful for that,
我还要感恩食物
but I'm also thankful for the food.
我也是 食物太美味了
Yeah, me too. The food. Amazing.
你不能抄我的 说你自己的
You can't piggy-back on my thanks. Have your own.
我感恩洛根身体好起来了 真的
I'm feeling thankful that Logan's better. Feel... Yeah.
我们都很感恩这点
Well, I think we're all thankful for that.
无需赘述
I think it goes without saying.
但... 没错 真的很开心
But... Yeah, I am. Really.
-该你了  -什么 我吗
- You. - What, me?
就是你
You.
我感恩自己不在难民营
Um, I'm grateful I'm not in a refugee camp.
因为这里比那儿好多了
I guess this is better than that.
你确实应该为此感恩
I think you should be thankful for that.
我们大家都这么想的 说得真棒
And so say all of us. That was a good one.
-我能说说吗  -说吧
- Can I say? - Go ahead.
我感恩能有机会主持欧洲分部的动画制作
I'm thankful for the opportunity to head up Animation in Europe,
希望我能让这个绩效不彰的部门焕然一新
and I hope to turn around an underperforming division.
那我就感恩你把这事告诉我们了
Well, I'm thankful that you told us about that, then.
-祝贺你  -谢谢
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
我感恩威拉在场
I'm thankful to have Willa here.
我感恩大家这么... 欢迎我
I'm thankful to be made to feel so... welcome.
我感恩我即将结婚
And I'm thankful that I am gonna be marrying
然后加入世界上最重要和最有趣...
into one of the most vital and interesting and...
最友善和关爱的家族
kind and loving families in the world.
你不娶小西了吗
Are you not gonna be marrying Shiv anymore?
既然咱们谈到家族了
Since we're talking about families,
我想小小地通知大家...
I have a little announcement. Uh...
威拉和我很高兴宣布 我已经请求过她
Willa and I are pleased to announce that I've asked her,
她也同意我们要...
and she's agreed that we are to...
迈出下一步了
take the next steps.
啥意思 你们不会是要结...
What? Y-You're not getting, uh...?
不是 我们...
No. We're...
打算稳定下来
goin' steady.
老天爷
Jesus Christ.
稳定下来 你还是九岁小孩吗
You're going steady? What are you, nine?
-怎么了  -为你高兴 老哥
- What? - Happy for you, man.
-谢谢  -非常棒 康纳
- Thanks. - Very nice, Connor.
谢谢
Thank you.
格蕾丝
Grace?
我吗 好吧...
Me? OK. Um...
我感恩罗曼对我的
I'm thankful for all the love
全部的关爱
Roman has shown to me,
感恩他从不自私 从不唯我独尊
and for never being selfish or self-centered
从不以自我为中心 神经质或不忠诚
or egocentric or neurotic or unfaithful.
不客气
You're welcome.
好 玩个游戏吧
OK. A game?
咱们玩个游戏吧
Shall we play a game?
-当然  -把孩子们叫过来吧
- Yeah. - Let's gather the kids.
行 来吧 宝贝们
OK, come on, kiddies.
什么游戏
What game?
你不想跟我们谈谈阿米尔的事吗
You didn't want to tell us about, uh, Amir?
-啥事  -咱们走吧
- What? - Shall we?
我们要谈阿米尔的什么事
What should we say about Amir?
他想知道阿米尔的事 我们要说什么
He wants to know about Amir. What should we say?
祝贺你迈入下一步了
Congratulations on your next steps.
-多谢了  -我很想知道
- Oh, thank you. - I'm interested to know
"下一步"到底是什么意思
what "Next steps" actually means.
我能买张贺卡 上面写着...
Is there a greeting card I can buy that says...
不必 你的好意我们心领了
No, your good wishes are all that's necessary.
会举行仪式呢 还是财务安排更多一点
Is there a ceremony or is it more a financial arrangement?
你给我听着
Hey, listen.
至少这里只有一位家族成员在搞我 懂了吗
At least I'm only getting fucked by one member of this family, yeah?
好 该你了
OK, your turn.
我去超市买了只小马驹
I went to the market and bought a pony,
一只胖母鸡和这个
a big fat hen, and this.
我去超市买了顶新帽子
OK. I went to the market and bought a new hat,
一只小马驹 一只胖母鸡和这个
a pony, a big fat hen, and this.
我去超市买了可卡因试管...
Uh, I went to the market and I bought a crack pipe...
-糟透了  -不行吗
- That's terrible. - No?
好吧 我去超市买了件紧身衣[SM]...
All right, I went to the market and I bought a gimp suit--
-别闹了  -我的天
- Come on! - Oh, my God.
我去超市买了颗土豆 一顶新帽子
I bought a potato, a new hat,
一只小马驹 一只胖母鸡和这个
a pony, a big fat hen, and this.
该你了
Your turn.
来吧 老爸 你想买个啥
All right. Come on, Dad, what's it gonna be?
热狗 中国或是永生之力
A hot dog, or China? Immortality?
还是国家之魂
The soul of the nation?
我去超市买了...
I went to market and I bought...
行 我知道
Yeah, OK.
我去超市
I went to market
买了...
and I bought...
...本地电视台
...local TV.
-他能买这个吗  -当然
- Can he buy that? - Yeah,
爸想买什么就买什么
Dad can buy whatever he wants.
-然后呢 本地电视台和...  -什么
- So? Local TV and...? - What?
时间不等人 快没时间了
The clock's tickin'. Time's runnin' out.
本地电视台加我刚才说的
Local TV and what did I say?
一颗土豆
A potato.
-这是作弊 不准提示  -别介啊
- Hey! That is cheating. No hints.  - No, come on.
来吧 爸 你能行的
Come on, Dad. You got this.
算了 咱们跳一轮
Come on, we can skip a turn.
玛西娅 你来
Marcia, you go.
-没事 他...  -你输了 爷爷
- No, he... - You lost, Grandpa.
你输了
You lose.
放手
Let go!
你没事吧
Are you all right?
你他妈在干什么
What the fuck are you doing?!
-还好吗  -没事吧
- Are you OK? - Are you all right?
我都没碰他 被吓到了而已
I hardly touched him. It's just shock.
-来吧 没事的  -放轻松 儿子 没事
- Come on, it's OK. - Relax, son, relax.
把你的手拿开 行吗
Hey, take your hands off him, OK?!
肯德尔
Kendall!
你他妈出了什么问题
What the fuck is wrong with you?!
别气了 没事的
It's OK. It's OK.
他伤到你了吗
Did he hurt you?
我看看
Let me see.
没事的 听我的话 你没事的
You're fine. Listen to me. You're OK.
-怎样  -我不敢相信
- Yeah? - I cannot believe it.
是啊
Yeah.
没事了
It's OK.
没事 没事
It's OK, it's OK.
-你还好吗  -还行
- You're OK? - Yeah, I'm good.
晚上好
Hey.
晚上好 格丽
Hey, Gerri.
尤恩之前想说什么啊 肯
So what was Ewan talking about earlier, Ken?
尤恩...
Ewan? Uh...
不知道
I don't know.
毕竟大家都很不高兴
I mean, everyone's pretty upset.
我不会太在意他
I wouldn't take any notice.
他为什么对你生那么大的气
Why was he so mad at you?
对我 不知道啊
At me? Uh, I don't know.
就是感恩节都会出现的日常埋怨
Just the usual family hatred you get at Thanksgiving.
你明白的
You know how it is.
我敬爱你的父亲
I love your dad.
我本人 是绝对不会背弃他的
Personally, I will always be there for him.
-他很伟大  -当然... 你都来了
- He's a great man. - Yeah, well... you're here.
但我为韦斯达工作 不是洛根·罗伊
I work for Waystar, not Logan Roy.
你是不是想动议反对他
Are you thinking of moving against him?
因为如果真是这样...
Because if you are...
我已经和弗兰克谈过了
I've spoken to Frank,
该看到的我都看到了
and I've seen all I need to see.
晚安
Good night.
咱们把衣服脱了
Let's take this off.
来 把手给我
Here. Give me your arm.
很好
Great.
好了
All right.
Right.
脱鞋
Your shoe.
我去超市...
I went to the market...
买了颗土豆...
and I bought a potato...
一顶新帽子
a new hat,
一只小马驹
a pony,
一只胖母鸡
a big fat hen,
和这个
and this.
对了 洛根
That's right, Logan.
全对了
That's great.
THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠